blogupp.com 2016-12-06

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

We take your privacy seriously and therefore, below we provide you with our privacy policy, where we intend to be transparent about any information we collect, how we intend to use it to your benefit, and what choices you have when you start using BlogUpp. Here are our commitments to you: 

  * Your privacy remains strictly under your control;
  * You can stop using BlogUpp service at any time;
  * We will never disclose your personally-identifiable information to any third party, unless you expressly have given us permission to do so or we are required to do so by law.

  1. **Information Collected by BlogUpp**  
Unlike most traditional web services, BlogUpp doesn't collect private information. This is mostly due to the fact that you can start using the service without registering an account with us at all.

Depending on how you interact with BlogUpp widget, you provide us with information, which may include: (a) your interaction with BlogUpp features, and (b) information you provide us when you contact us for help or with feedback, as well as enable social networking features. We collect other non-personally identifiable data, which may include your IP address and what browser you are using so that we can improve BlogUpp service to you. 

  2. **Use of Information**  
We may use the non-personally identifiable information, like your IP address, to analyze statistical site usage and to customize our site's content, layout and services. The resulting information will allow us to improve our services and better understand and serve our users. 

We do not sell user lists, i.e. the list of participating sites. We will not share any information that identifies you personally with any third party unless it is necessary to fulfill a transaction you have requested, in other circumstances in which you have consented to the sharing of your information, or except as described in this Privacy Policy. We occasionally may share information with other companies that work on our behalf to help provide our services to you, provided that they are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose. We will disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority or to protect our rights and property or the rights and property of the public. We may also cooperate with law enforcement agencies in any official investigation and we may disclose your personally identifiable information to the relevant agency in doing so. 

  3. **Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are a standard Internet technology, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features for their users. We use cookies with BlogUpp to allow us to improve the quality of our service, store user preferences, and to personalize content and offers of interest to our users. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of BlogUpp if you do so. 
  4. **Links to Other Sites**  
Through BlogUpp widget we present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our technology, customized content and advertising. 

Note that BlogUpp can be used through Google Gadgets, Widgetbox gallery, or other widget directory. This Privacy Policy applies to web sites, services and applications that are owned and provided by us and we are not responsible for the privacy policies, practices or contents of any third party websites. Please refer to the privacy policies of such third party websites for information on what kinds of personally identifiable information such websites collect and their respective privacy practices, terms, and conditions. 

  5. **Acquisition**  
We reserve the right to transfer the information that identifies you in the event of a transfer of ownership of BlogUpp, such as acquisition by or merger with another company. If an acquiring company should plan to materially change this privacy policy, we will notify you beforehand. 
  6. **Security**  
We take steps to help protect your information. We require password protection physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect information about you. Please note however that no technological environment is completely secure and we cannot guarantee the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to BlogUpp over the Internet. If you have any other questions about the security of our website and service, please contact us. 
  7. **Changes in Privacy Policy**  
From time to time we may update this Privacy Policy and will post a notice of any significant changes on our website. You should visit this page periodically to review any such changes to the privacy policy. Your continued use of our service will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy. 
  8. **Canceling the Use of the Service**  
You always have the option to stop using the service. Simply remove the widget from your site. Advertisers may request to have their campaigns stopped by submitting a request by email. We will act on your request as promptly as possible. 
  9. **How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or concerns about BlogUpp Privacy Policy or its implementation, please contact us by using "Support" link from the menu. 
  10. This policy is effective as of March 04, 2008.
